

About

An iOS engineer with a background in SAP industry. Passionate about crafting great user experience while developing clean, modular code. Motivated self-learner keen to learn new technologies to build better, more efficient solutions. A huge fan of smart homes technology and dog whisperer.

Experience

MultiPeer Selfie 2018 to Current

Tech Stack: (Multipeer Connectivity, AVFoundation)

• This selfie taking app solves the problem people often struggle with when taking a selfie in a group. It sets up one device as the camera, multiple connected devices as remote. The app synchronizes and saves the photo to all the remote devices upon pressing the shutter button

AR BeerPon 2018 to Current

Tech Stack: (Firebase, Cloud Anchor, ARKit, SceneKit, Core Animation)

 A multiplayer beer pong game in augmented reality that uses ARKit and SceneKit to setup beer pong scene, synchronize game state and object transformation in 3D world in realtime using Firebase and Google Cloud Anchor

HeadsUP 2018 to Current

Tech Stack: (Firebase, Core Location, GeoFire, MapKit)

- The app uses MapKit and Core Location to display user location on the map, GeoFire to detect nearby user within certain radius; and Firebase manages all the connections for each user
- The purpose of this app is to promote people to meet new friends and talk to people instead of looking down on their phones

Employment

Sompo Purchase, NY SAP Senior Business Analyst March 2017 to Oct. 2017

Involved in FS-RI and FS-CD implementation from requirement gathering to go live phase

Virtusa

New York, NY
SAP Technical Consultant

June 2013 to Feb. 2017

Client: ADP (06/2016 - 02/2017)

SAP Technical Consultant

- Worked on Electronic Federal Tax Payment System implementation to help clients to file taxes for their employees
- · Configured SAP Gateway to connect with the front end system

Client: CareSource (04/2015 - 05/2016)

SAP Technical Consultant

 Worked on FS-CD implementation to automate their incoming payment process and payment clarification process

Client: United Guarantee (09/2013 - 03/2015)

SAP Techno-Functional Consultant

- Created and performed technical unit testings, user acceptance testings and user security testing for various processes
- Conducted requirement workshops with business users and project team for billing, payment and disbursement processes

Contact

▼ ruijialin@gmail.com

**** 7184960737

in ruijialin

nayjialin

Education

Lighthouse Labs

2018

Immersive iOS Development Bootcamp 2018

Barnard Baruch College

Computer Information Systems 2013

Skills

LANGUAGES

Swift

Objective-C

C

Ruby

Javascript

HTML

CSS

ABAP

FRAMEWORKS & TESTING TOOLS

Core Animation

Foundation

Core Location

MapKit

AVKit

Parse

Realm

Firebase

Core Data

Cloud Anchor

UlKit

Core Graphics

ARKit

XCTest

DESIGN PATTERNS

MVC

MVVM

Delegation

KV0